

# Gabrielle AZADIAN COET

# Software Engineer

#### **ABOUT**

I have 8 years of experience in commercial architecture. This experience within Unibail-Rodmaco Westfield has allowed me to acquire qualities such as teamwork, creativity, rigour and reactivity. Working as a temp allowed me to acquire other strenghts such as flexibility, networking, scheduling and adaptability. Today, I am looking for new opportunities as a

## CONTACT

software engineer.

+33(0)6 64 38 81 12



gabrielleazadian@gmail.com



Hansjakobstr. 80, 81673 München



https://github.com/gabrielle2801



https://www.linkedin.com/in/gabrielle-azadian-coet-b2928175/

### **EDUCATION**

**PYTHON Application Developer Training** Master

OpenClassRooms 2020 - 2022

Magister Interior Design / Design with honors Académie Charpentier Paris 75006, France 2005 - 2011

BTS minor development St Gabriel Bagneux, France 2001-2003

# LANGUAGES

French Mother Tongue Armenian C1 English B2

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Retail 3D April 2019 Korian nursing home project Autocad, Sketch'up, Adobe Suite

Cba March 2019 Shopping center project in Switzerland Autocad, Adobe Suite

Intersport October 2018 - February 2019 2D and 3D design shop Autocad, Sketch'Up, Adobe Suite

Unibail-Rodamco Westfield June 2012 - September 2018 3D design of shopping center on ARCHIcad and Atlantis rendering Shopping Center project shopfront (Ikea, Adidas, Galeries Lafayette) Archicad, Sketch'up, Atlantis, Adobe Suite

High School Le Rebours internship 5 months 2003 intranet PHP / Mysql Photoshop

Tricot Reine internship 5 months 2002 Database mysql / VB Application to view autumn/winter and spring/summer collection

#### SKILL

#### HARD

Python Django

Flask

CSS / HTML5

SGBD: postgresl, mysql, positco, pgAdmin

Class Diagram

**UML** 

Users Stories

#### SOFT

Creativity Teamwork Adaptability Active Listening

#### MAD







